const riddles = [
  {
    question:
      "I swing through trees and eat bananas, With a tail that helps me balance in all my manners. Who am I?",
    answer: "A monkey",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I have a mane and a mighty roar, I'm the king of the jungle, hear me roar. Who am I?",
    answer: "A lion",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I'm big and gray with a trunk for a nose, In the savanna, I'm where everyone goes. Who am I?",
    answer: "An elephant",
  },
  {
    question:
      "With stripes of black and white, I stand, In the grasslands, you’ll see my band. Who am I?",
    answer: "A zebra",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I live in the Arctic and swim in the sea, A white coat is what you’ll see. Who am I?",
    answer: "A polar bear",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In the bamboo forest, I munch and play, With black and white fur, I'm cute all day. Who am I?",
    answer: "A panda",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I'm known for my speed on African plains, Fastest of all, I’ll win any race. Who am I?",
    answer: "A cheetah",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I live in the water but breathe air, With my big teeth, I’m quite a scare. Who am I?",
    answer: "A hippopotamus",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I’m colorful and squawk from tree to tree, With a hooked beak, you’ll surely see me. Who am I?",
    answer: "A parrot",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I slither on the ground without a sound, My venom can bring you down. Who am I?",
    answer: "A snake",
  },
];
